hello thank you for thank you for calling Omni tech support my name is
Marco how may I help you today yeah hi Marco how are you today I'm good how are
you man I'm not really good I have a problem with your service the internet
got caught and I'm working from home I've called three times every time your
friends previously gave me different timing for the internet to come back I
just want to confirm when the internet is coming back I understand you're upset
ma'am I'm sorry to hear you're experiencing an issue with your service
can I please have the phone number on your account associates with your
account so I can pull up details yeah it's eight eight two four mm-hmm all
right eight eight two four five three mm-hmm seven six five three yes once again
so eight eight two four seven six five three nine one yes okay so it's eight
eight two four seven six five three nine one yeah and the name is this is Sarah
Sarah Sarah Thompson am I right yeah all right thank you miss Thompson I see your
account here yes I do see a documented service interruption in your area due to
a fiber line cut it looks like the estimated time for resolution is 8 p.m.
Eastern by today well I've been given three different timing I hope this time is
finite because I've been suffering from this for the last 48 hours and I'm
working from home and you know all my work collapsed and I have to respond to
people and get in touch with people meeting to attend and all these things
it's not like you know it's very frustrating I understand and let me just
check again okay here's what the field team is reporting right now they've
identified the specific point of failure and they've already begun splicing new
cable and based on the complexity of the repair I can see that the new and I
assure you firm estimate for the full restoration is within the next four
hours by 8 p.m. Eastern okay then why why the application keeps shifting the
timing like you know it's like a moving target kept moving from time to time it's
not like you know maybe I will hang up with you now and then again they will
change the time to different timing it is true the application has seen some
glitches and I understand miss Thompson once your service is fully restored we
will be happily processing an adjustment to your bill and we would happily
give you a $25 inconvenience credit for the trouble that you've gone through
would that be okay yeah that's fine as long as the internet will be back soon you
said what time 8 p.m. 8 p.m. today yes ma'am so that is after four hours from now mm-hmm
that's correct okay and you will reimburse $25 ma'am and
we will deduct any internet usage in between these these hours and these days
that you haven't used the internet from your bill for this month okay all right
is there anything else if the cable did not get connected by 8 p.m. what what
should I do please call us again on and but I assure you it will be connected by
8 p.m. but if by any chance it did not get connected please do call us again and we
will be happily assisting you for the problem
well I'll try to call you if it is not connected I won't be happy but I'll try
to contact you all right no worries ma'am we're here for you okay okay is there
anything else I may help you with no thank you Michael thank you for calling
OmniTech support have a good evening
me
I'll try you
you