good afternoon thank you for calling the sandstone beach resort my name is Marco and I'll be happy
to assist you hi Marco my name is Anna I'm calling because I just booked a stay for my husband and
me and we're absolutely thrilled like your resort looks so good in the pictures that's wonderful
Anna we can't wait to welcome you I'll be happy to pull up your reservation can I please have your
last name and confirmation number certainly the last name is Davis and the confirmation number is
SB seven seven three nine zero two SP seven seven nine seven seven three nine zero two right yes
that's the one it's our tenth wedding anniversary trip and we've been saving up for this I just
wanted to confirm that the all-inclusive meal plan is definitely included as I selected all right one
second miss Davis let me just search it up all right thank you miss Davis sorry for interrupting you I see
it right here you have a reservation for the sunset ocean view suite for five nights checking in on
June 15th is that correct oh thank goodness yeah that's perfect we can't wait to try the seafood grill
now I have one little favor to ask if possible since it's our anniversary is there any chance we could
request a room on a higher floor we'd love the best possible view that's a beautiful request for a special
occasion wait let me check if there's availability for the request for 15th one second all right good
news miss Davis I see we have a gorgeous suite available on the 12th floor which is one of our
highest I've gone ahead and placed a firm request for that specific room for you that is absolutely
wonderful thank you so much for doing that that is going to make the trip so special my pleasure
miss Davis we want your anniversary to be perfect as a little extra thank you I've also added a note
for a complimentary bottle of sparkling wine and a small dessert plate to be waiting in your room upon
arrival you're just making my day that is so thoughtful thank you again you've been so helpful it's
truly my job and my pleasure we look forward to celebrating your anniversary with you and your
husband so just to recap reservation is confirmed the all-inclusive plan is active and you have the
12th floor view request confirmed plus an anniversary retreat is there anything else I can assist you
with regarding your upcoming stay we'll be waiting have a wonderful day Anna